Finding Aid for the CBS Inc. Film and Television Collection PASC-M.0072
UCLA Library Special Collections
CBS Inc. film and television collection
1955-1991
UCLA Library Special Collections
CBS Inc.
PASC-M.0072
1550.5 linear feet (3101 boxes)
The collection consists of music manuscripts, books, printed music, sound recordings and business papers relating to CBS productions. Also included are logs, music manuscripts, books, and printed music related to four types of CBS productions: features films, television series, television specials, and television movies, The productions fall under the CBS Television Network, CBS Entertainment Division, CBS Productions Network, and, in a few cases, earlier manifestations of these divisions. The collection includes materials in the form of: manuscript scores, parts, and a few Ozalid masters of both scores and parts for film and television productions; printed sheet music and folios of popular music; publishers catalogs, brochures; published books about music; and published silent film music. The collection includes materials by composers such as Jeff Alexander, Bill "Rocky" Conti, Jerry Goldsmith, Bernard Herrmann, Henry Mancini, Lyn Murray, Alex North, Fred Steiner, Dimitri Tiomkin, Franz Waxman, and John Williams. Productions represented include TV series such as Gilligan's Island, Gunsmoke, Have Gun Will Travel, Hawaii 5-0, Perry Mason, Rawhide, Twilight Zone, and Wild Wild West. Also included is music for feature films such as The April Fools, Little Big Man, The Reivers, Rio Lobo, and Table For Five. A highlight of the collection are many scores for live Playhouse 90 dramas.
Conditions Governing Access
Portions of collection unprocessed. Material in Series 13: Sound Recordings and Subserires 10.2: Popular Music Sheet Music is unavailable for access. Please contact Special Collections reference (spec-coll@library.ucla.edu) for more information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of CBS Inc., 1988.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942326713606533
Biography/History
CBS Broadcasting Inc. (CBS) is one of the largest radio and television networks in the United States. The name is derived from the initials of Columbia Broadcasting System, its former legal name.
The network has its origins in United Independent Broadcasters Inc., a collection of 16 radio stations that was bought by William S. Paley in 1928 and renamed the Columbia Broadcasting System. Under Paley's guidance, CBS would first become one of the largest radio networks in the United States and then one of the big three American broadcast television networks. In 1974, CBS dropped its full name and became known simply as CBS, Inc. The Westinghouse Electric Corporation acquired the network in 1995 and eventually adopted the name of the company it had bought to become CBS Corporation. In 2000, CBS came under the control of Viacom, which coincidentally had begun as a spin-off of CBS in 1971. In late 2005, Viacom split itself and reestablished CBS Corporation with the CBS television network at its core. CBS Corporation and the new Viacom are controlled by Sumner Redstone through National Amusements, the parent of the two companies.
Scope and Content
The CBS Inc. film and television collection consists of music manuscripts, logs, books, printed music, sound recordings and business papers relating to documentaries, features films, mini series, television programs and made for television movies. The productions fall under the CBS Television Network, CBS Entertainment Division, CBS Productions Network, and, in a few cases, earlier manifestations of these divisions.
The collection includes materials in the form of: manuscript scores, parts, and select Ozalid masters of both scores and parts for film and television productions; printed sheet music and folios of popular music; publishers catalogs, brochures; financial and business records, recording logs, and sound recordings.
Included in the collection are materials by composers such as Jeff Alexander, Bill "Rocky" Conti, Jerry Goldsmith, Bernard Herrmann, Henry Mancini, Lyn Murray, Alex North, Fred Steiner, Dimitri Tiomkin, Franz Waxman, and John Williams.
Productions represented include TV series such as Gilligan's Island, Gunsmoke, Have Gun Will Travel, Hawaii 5-0, Perry Mason, Rawhide, Twilight Zone, and Wild Wild West. The collection also includes music for feature films such as The April Fools, Little Big Man, The Reivers, Rio Lobo, and Table For Five. Also included are many scores for live Playhouse 90 dramas.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in the following series:
Series 1. Documentaries
Series 2. Feature Films
Series 3. Mini Series
Series 4. Television Programs
Series 5. Television Movies
Series 6. Unidentified Programs, Films, etc.
Series 7. Business Papers
Series 8. Clippings, 1976-1988. 1 folder
Series 9. Radio Programs
Series 10. Published Music
Series 12. Recording Logs
Series 13. Sound Recordings -- Unprocessed
Series 14. Radio
Series 15. Unidentified Materials
Television music -- Scores and parts.; Music -- Manuscripts.; Motion picture music -- Scores and parts.; CBS Inc.--Archives.
- Documentaries, Series 1.
  - The African Elephant -- Sound Recordings, 1971 April 13-October 4; Subseries 1.; 7 sound recordings
    Arrangement note
    Identified items follow those that are unidentified.
    Scope and Contents note
    Simon Trevor follows an elephant from almost the moment of its birth through the seasons as it grows and learns.
    - Log 440, 1971 June 9; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 1)
      General note
      On container, "CCF/6-9-71/R92ADD/Log 440-CCF248/PNO & vocal demo/#5083 Elephant."
    - Log 527, 1971 July 29; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 2)
      On container, "CCF/7-29-71/R96ADD/LOG527-DD1/5083-African Elephant "Rainfalls" (Theme) Vocal."
    - Unidentified, 1971 April 13-26; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 6)
      On container, "CCF/Recorded in England 4-13-71 thru 4-15-71 and 4-26-71/R79DD/M6382 and 90/African Elephant."
    - Unidentified, 1971 April 13-26; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 7)
      On container, "CCF/Recorded in England 4-13-71 through 4-15-71 and 4-26-71 DD Studio Center/R80 DD/M91-103/African Elephant."
    - Unidentified, 1971 April 13-23; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 11)
      On container, "CCF/Recorded in England 4-13-71 through 4-15-71 and 4-22-71 DD Studio Center/R77DD/M10-24 and 30/African Elephant."
    - Unidentified, 1971 April 13-23; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 12)
      On container, "CCF/Recorded in England 4-13-71 through 4-15-71 and 4-23-71 DD Studio Center/R78DD/M31-62/African Elephant."
    - Unidentified, 1971 October 4; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1125, Folder 4)
      On container, "CF/10-4-71/R101A/CCF 371 - M103 - Orch Only/CCF 372 - M104 - Orch + Vocal/#5083 "African Elephant"."
  - The African Elephant -- Scores, Subseries 2.; 2 boxes
    - Assorted Cues, orchestral scores (Box 34)
    - Assorted Cues, orchestral scores (Box 35)
      cue 103
- Feature Films, Series 2.
  - Adam at Six A.M. -- Scores, Subseries 32.
    - Adam at Six A.M., orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 20 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 037
    - Apple Pie, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 6 (Box 26)
      three copies... on item: CCF 025
    - Board Fade Heaven, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 1 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 002
    - Chase, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 4 (Box 26)
      four copies... on item: CCF 028
    - Deasy at the Daisy, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 3 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 001
    - Elijah, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 8 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 036
    - Elijah, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 4 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 010
    - Elijah, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 5 (Box 26)
    - Elijah Rise Up, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 2 (Box 26)
      on item: CCF 035
    - Jerry Jo, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 7 (Box 26)
      four copies... on item: CCF 012
    - Lonely Phone, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 5 (Box 26)
      five copies... on item: CCF 023
    - Neighbors, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 11 (Box 26)
      four copies... on item: CCF 026
    - Party, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 3 (Box 26)
      four copies... on item: CCF 031
    - Party Part II, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 3 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 034
    - Pool Party, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 12 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 005
    - Solitaire Forever, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 2 (Box 26)
      four copies... on item: CCF 030
    - Sunshine, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 7 (Box 26)
      four copies... on item: CCF 024
    - Tiger by the Tail, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 3 (Box 26)
      on item: CCF 019
    - UCLA, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 10 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 004
    - Valhalla Vale, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 16 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 007
    - Welcome Home, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 12 (Box 26)
      four copies... on item: CCF 014
    - Work Call, orchestral score from "Adam at Six A.M." 2 (Box 26)
      two copies... on item: CCF 017
  - Adam at Six A.M. -- Sound Recordings, 1970-1971; Subseries 1.; 5 sound recordings
    Items identified by log numbers follow those that are unidentified.
    Plot: Disenchanted young Professor of Semantics at a California college learns of a distant relative's death in Missouri. Production No. 1316-5107-0000
    - Logs 179, 185, 187, 1971 June 20-July 1; open reel audio tape (Box 1088, Folder 10)
      On container, "CCF/6-29-71 and 7-1-71/R71ADD/M11A and M103A Logs 179, 185 and 187/#5107-Adam at Six A.M.."
    - Unidentified, 1970 April 24; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1125, Folder 15)
      On container, "CCF/R61A DD/M 112 + 112A/#5107 Adam at 6 AM/Production No. 1316-5107-0000."
    - Unidentified, 1970 April 22; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1125, Folder 17)
      On container, "CCF/R60A DD/M91/112/#5107 - Adam at 6 A.M.."
    - Unidentified, 1970 April 22; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1125, Folder 18)
      On container, "CCF/R59A DD/M52-91/#5107 - Adam at 6 A.M.."
    - Unidentified, 1970 April 22; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1128, Folder 15)
      On container, "CCF/R58A/M11-61/#5107 Adam At 6 A.M.."
  - The April Fools -- Recording Logs, 1969; Subseries 2.
    - Recording Logs, April 1969; 57 pages
      Soloists include: Susan Barrett, Dionne Warwick, and Harvey Korman. Includes cues, timings, orchestration, place and time of recording sessions, etc. Found in: 1968/69 season black binder arranged chronologically.
  - The April Fools -- Scores, 1969; Subseries 3.
    - Scores, 1969 April (Box 33)
  - The April Fools -- Sound Recordings, 1969; Subseries 4.
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape (Box 1092, Folder 12)
      On container, "CCF/B15A-DD/M33-104+12x/#5020-April Fools."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape (Box 1092, Folder 13)
      On container, "CCF/B14A-DD/M36 & 40-71/#5020-April Fools."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape (Box 1092, Folder 14)
      On container, "CCF/B13A-DD/M11-35/#5020-April Fools."
  - Back Roads -- Scores, Subseries 38.
    - Scores (Box 143)
  - Back Roads -- Sound Recordings, 1980-1981; Subseries 5.; 39 sound recordings
    Unidentified items are followed by those that are identified.
    Plot: A prostitute and a drifter find themselves bound together as they make their way through the rural South, doing what they have to do to survive.
    - Back Roads, Cassette tape (Box 1868)
      Back Roads Main title -- California On My Mind Bus Montage.
    - California on My Mind, 1981 February 2; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1022, Folder 4)
      Title from container. On container, "Back Roads/"Calif. On My Mind"/R-3/2-2-81."
    - Stand and Deliver -- Sound recordings, open reel audio tape (Box 1851)
      Container notes that title is formally "Walking on Water."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 960, Folder 1)
      On container, "Reel 2/Back Roads/2."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 960, Folder 2)
      On container, "Reel 3/Back Roads/3."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 960, Folder 3)
      On container, "Reel 4/B.R./4."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 960, Folder 4)
      On container, "Reel 5/B.R./5."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 960, Folder 5)
      On container, "Reel 6/B.R./6."
    - Unidentified, 1981 January 27; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 971, Folder 2)
      On container, "81-5/Waylon Jennings/Back Roads versions #1, #2, #3."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 17; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 971, Folder 3)
      On container, ""Back Roads"/24 trk/30 IPS/2-17-81/R-1."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 2; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 971, Folder 4)
      On container, ""Back Roads"/Versions 1, 2, 3/15 IPS/24 Trks/Waylon Jennings/Dolby/2-2-81/R1."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 972, Folder 5)
      On container, "Reel 1/Back Roads."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 17; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 975, Folder 1)
      On container, ""Back Roads"/24 trk/30 IPS/2-17-81/R-3."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 2; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1009, Folder 2)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-1/2-2-81."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 17; open reel audio tape (Box 1009, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/"Back Roads"/1/4/2-17-81/R1/Dub Down Reel."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1009, Folder 6)
      On container, "B.R./Revised/10M1/10M2/9M1/3 Track."
    - Unidentified, 1981 January 19; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1009, Folder 7)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-1/10M3/1-19-81."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 20; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1010, Folder 19)
      On container, "Reel 1/15IPS/1.,2. Stereo Audio LR/3. FX/4. Sync."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 20; open reel audio tape (Box 1013, Folder 3)
      On container, "Reel #1/1st/71/2 IPS/2 Tr. Stereo/12-80."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 20; open reel audio tape (Box 1013, Folder 4)
      On container, "Reel Two/1 Audio/2 Sync/15 IPS."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 19; open reel audio tape (Box 1013, Folder 5)
      On container, "Reel One/1 Audio/2 Sync/15 IPS."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 17; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1013, Folder 7)
      On container, "CBS/"Back Roads"/1/2" MX/2-17-81/R2."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape (Box 1014, Folder 5)
      On container, "Reel Three/15 IPS/2 Track/Audio, Sync/Back Roads."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December; open reel audio tape (Box 1014, Folder 3)
      On container, "Reel #2/12-80/7 1/2 IPS/2 TR Stereo."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 20; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1013, Folder 9)
      On container, "12-20-80/Reel 3/15 IPS/Stereo Audio LR/FX/Sync/Alignment Tones 0 VU at leadered end of this reel."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape (Box 1014, Folder 4)
      On container, "9 MI/Bass, Gult (Consecutive Order, Not Together)/B.R./15 IPS/Mono."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 17; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1014, Folder 20)
      On container, "CBS/Back Roads/1/2" MX/2-17-81/R1/Dub-Down Reel."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 20; open reel audio tape (Box 1022, Folder 1)
      On container, "Tatle Song Reel (Rough Mixes)/Back Roads/12-20-80."
    - Unidentified, 1981 January 19; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1022, Folder 2)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-2/10 M3/1-19-81."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 2; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1022, Folder 3)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-2/2-2-81."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 30; open reel audio tape (Box 1022, Folder 5)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-1/12-30-80."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 30; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1022, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified, 1981 January 5; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1022, Folder 7)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-1/Protection Master 1/2"/1-5-81."
    - Unidentified, 1981 January 5; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1022, Folder 8)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-2/1/2" Protection Master/1-5-81."
    - Unidentified, 1981 January 5; open reel audio tape, 1/2 in. (Box 1022, Folder 9)
      On container, "Back Roads/R-3/1/2" Protection Master/1-5-81."
    - Unidentified, 1980 December 20; open reel audio tape (Box 1023, Folder 3)
      On container, "Reel 2/15 IPS/12-20-80/1. + 2. Stereo Audio LR/3. FX/4. Sync."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 17; open reel audio tape (Box 1023, Folder 4)
      On container, "CBS/"Back Roads"/1/4" Mix/2-17-81/R-2."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 1025, Folder 4)
      On container, "Reel 7/B.R./7."
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 1025, Folder 5)
      On container, "Reel 8/B.R./10 M1 10 M2 9 M1>Revised/8."
    - Unidentified, 1981 February 17; open reel audio tape, 2 in. (Box 1037, Folder 8)
      On container, "Back Roads/24 track/30 IPS/2-17-81/R-2."
  - Beverly Hills Cop -- Sound recordings, Subseries 6.; 1 sound recordings
    - Berverly Hills Cop, open reel audio tape (Box 1851)
      Contents: Will You Respect Me (in the Mornin') -- Animal Instinct -- Something in the Way -- Breakdown -- Got to Find a Reason.
  - Blue Water White Death -- Sound Recordings, 1971 May 21; Subseries 7.; 2 sound recordings
    - Unidentified, 1971 May 21; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1146, Folder 3)
      On container, "Roll 17977/Studio Center R4-5/Blue Water White Death/5-21-71."
    - Unidentified, 1971 May 21; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1146, Folder 4)
      On container, "Roll 17976/Studio Center R1-2-3/Blue Water White Death/5-21-71."
  - A Boy Named Charlie Brown -- Sound Recordings, 1969 October 14-15; Subseries 8.; 3 sound recordings
    Arranged chronologically.
    - Unidentified, open reel audio tape (Box 947, Folder 10)
      On container, "2096/2/Mendelson Melendez/A Boy Named Charlie Brown."
    - Unidentified, 1969 October 14; open reel audio tape, 1 in. (Box 1146, Folder 10)
      On container, "C2096/Mendelson Melendez/Charlie Brown/Reel No. 1."
    - Unidentified, 1969 October 15; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1147, Folder 18)
      On container, "54675 Mono/Mendelsohn-Melendez/C-2096."
  - The Christian Licorice Store -- Sound Recordings, 1971 July 1; Subseries 9.; 1 sound recordings
    - Unidentified, 1971 July 1; open reel audio tape, 1/4 in. (Box 1146, Folder 11)
      On container, "CCF/7-1-71 7-2-71/R94A/DD 14-29/#5105 - Christian Licorice Store."
  - Darker Than Amber -- Scores, Subseries 27.
    - 19 Genuine Art Poses, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 30)
      on item: CCF #1316-5034-0000
    - Alabama Tiger - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 30)
    - Alabama Tiger - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 32)
    - All Ashore, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 18 (Box 30)
    - All Ashore, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 18 (Box 32)
    - The Battle of B-Deck, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 20 (Box 30)
    - The Battle of B-Deck, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 20 (Box 32)
    - The Best of Life, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 16 (Box 30)
    - The Best of Life, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 16 (Box 32)
    - The Blistered Flesh, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 10 (Box 30)
    - The Blistered Flesh, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 10 (Box 32)
    - Burk's Ass, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 11 (Box 30)
    - Burk's Ass, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 11 (Box 32)
    - Burk's Landing, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 30)
    - Burk's Landing, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 32)
    - The Busted Flush, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 5 (Box 30)
    - The Busted Flush, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 5 (Box 32)
    - End Credits, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 13 (Box 30)
    - End Credits, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 13 (Box 32)
    - The Festered Bush - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 30)
    - The Festered Bush - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 32)
    - Flamenco With Fatso - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 30)
    - Flamenco With Fatso - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 32)
    - Flashback Overlay, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 2 (Box 30)
    - Flashback Overlay, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 2 (Box 32)
    - The Flushed Bust - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 32)
    - The Flushed Bust - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 30)
    - Get Along, Little Doggie, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 4 (Box 30)
    - Get Along, Little Doggie, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 4 (Box 32)
    - Main Title, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 33 (Box 30)
    - Main Title, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 33 (Box 32)
    - Marymae, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 8 (Box 30)
    - Marymae, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 8 (Box 32)
    - Marymae - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 12 (Box 30)
    - Marymae - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 12 (Box 32)
    - Memories, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 30)
    - Memories, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 32)
    - The Morgue, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 2 (Box 30)
    - The Morgue, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 2 (Box 32)
    - My Name's Vangie, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 30)
    - My Name's Vangie, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 32)
    - My Name's Vangie, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 32)
    - My Name's Vangie, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 9 (Box 30)
    - 19 Genuine Art Poses, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 32)
    - Reincarnation?, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 3 (Box 30)
    - Reincarnation?, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 3 (Box 32)
    - Sand Crab, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 2 (Box 30)
    - Sand Crab, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 2 (Box 32)
    - Steel Band I - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 13 (Box 30)
    - Steel Band I - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 13 (Box 32)
    - Steel Band II - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 30)
    - Steel Band II - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 7 (Box 32)
    - Sunward, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 17 (Box 30)
    - Sunward, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 17 (Box 32)
    - Sunward, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 17 (Box 32)
    - Sunward Trio I - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 12 (Box 30)
    - Sunward Trio I - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 12 (Box 32)
    - Sunward Trio I - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 32)
    - Sunward Trio I - Source, orchestral score from "Darker than Amber" 6 (Box 30)